SL lup. Some call it sloop 332 and TRT.
Is it worth it? Man, I had to even go I
had to go look dig into this rabbit
trail because I I don't keep up with a
lot of the hyped peptides right now
because they're just it's insane how I
get like five or six messages a day
about peptides right now when I mean a
year ago it was it was hardly anything.
So I don't know if people are hyping
these up on talk shows all of a sudden
right now. I assume they are. Um, I mean
these peptides, a lot of them have been
around for years. Bodybuilders have been
playing with these things for a long
time. Most of them go in the trash bin
because they realize they don't do what
they're promised, you know. Um, the
Slooh from the only paper I really could
find on it that was worth reading. Um,
again, the problems are people think
you're going to find exercise in a pill
or an injection. You're not. You're
chasing markers that they equate with
exercise. But just because you can look
at certain markers of things like fatty
acid oxidation or whatever doesn't mean
that that's happening for the same
reason as it does in exercise. This is
the same mistake I see people make in a
lot of like the carnivore groups and
everything when they associate, you
know, fatty acid utilization with
burning body fat. Oh, your body's
switched over to burning or the keto
group. They've been saying this forever,
right? You're burning fat as fuel now.
It's like that has nothing to do with
whether you're losing body fat or not.
uh first of all and so and if you look
at the actual study done in these mutant
mice who are not humans the numbers and
the differences achieved were not that
different if you look at the actual
scatter plots not just the bars but go
look at the individual variations
between the groups they're all over the
place. So this is another problem with
statistics, you know, is that you can
make anything kind of look significant
when if you look at the individuals,
you're like, well, it didn't matter for
that one. It didn't matter for that one.
That one still gained weight and this
one didn't, you know, and so that would
be my concern is that people are people
are always chasing the the the easy fix.
And if if this works, I mean, if you
take it and you lose fat by not changing
anything, more power to you. But you
don't know how that's doing that in the
body. you don't any claims that you know
exactly what all these medicines are
doing to the body as a whole. You don't
know what they're doing. Um and so I you
know it's my same concern I have in a
similar fashion with the GLP1s and
things like that. I mean do they work?
Yes. Do we know how those work? Yeah. In
general I mean you're stopping the gut
from doing what it's supposed to do so
you feel full, right? I mean you're
essentially paralyzing your gut and
inducing gastroparesis. Uh any of these
claims about what it does in the brain
it you can't validate it. Um in general
we know how those work. these other
ones. I don't know. I mean, look at like
DNP. I mean, that works, but it ain't
healthy. It ain't safe, you know, and
all and bodybuilders know that. They
admit it. And I think that's the main
thing here is like if you educate
yourself on these things enough to go,
okay, I don't really know how this thing
may work. It may not be healthy, but I
don't care. I want to try this as a
guinea pig for myself. More, that's
great because then you have informed
consent to do it. You have all the
information. My problem is when these
things are just pushed as miracle drugs
or and they don't nobody goes into like
okay but watch out for this this and
this and we don't know what it's doing.
They'll just pushes you got to take this
thing man it's it's a miracle and it's
just not um but yeah the study I found
the main study I could only find was
really one study in these mutant mice.
Everything else were peptide research
chemical websites promoting it. So again
there's no issue taking it with or
without TRT. I don't think the TRT part
has anything to do with it. like TRT is
its own category. Um I don't see that
conflicting with any other experimental
peptides somebody wants to take per se.